groovyhistory.com 2018-06-15

# Privacy Policy | Groovy History

GroovyHistory Privacy Policy

We at GroovyHistory (“GroovyHistory,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) created this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) because we know that you care about how information you provide to us is used and shared. This Privacy Policy relates to the information collection and use practices of GroovyHistory in connection with our website located at https://www.GroovyHistory.com/ (the “Site”), and the Service.

By visiting our Site and/or using our Service, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the accompanying Terms of Use. Capitalized terms not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning set forth in our Terms of Use.

Information we collect

We do not collect any personal information from you unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

When you sign up to become a Registered User, you will be asked to provide us with certain personal information, such as your name and email address. If you register through Facebook Connect, Twitter or other Social Media websites, those Social Media websites will provide us with certain personal information in connection with the registration process. In this Privacy Policy, we refer to this information as “Personal Information.”

Like most web sites, we use automatic data collection technology when you visit our Site to record information that identifies your computer, to track your use of our Site, and to collect certain basic information about you and your surfing habits. This information includes information about your operating system, your IP addresses, browser type and language, referring and exit pages and URLs, keywords, date and time, amount of time spent on particular pages, what sections of a website you visit, and similar information concerning your use of the Site and the Services, including information about your sharing habits and patterns (the “Usage Information”).

We collect this Usage Information by using cookies and pixel tags (also called web beacons or clear gifs). Cookies are small packets of data that a website stores on your computer’s hard drive so that your computer will “remember” information about your visit. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of web site users. You can reject cookies by following the directions provided in your Internet provider’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still visit the Site, but may not be able to use some areas of the Site and/or the Service.

We do not collect personally identifying information in this way, but if you’ve provided us with personally identifying information we may associate that information with the information that is collected automatically. Automatic data collection may be performed on our behalf by our services providers. We may also allow third-party companies that are presenting advertisements on the Site to set and access their own cookies. Such third-party cookies are not governed by this Privacy Policy, but by the privacy policies of such third party.

Our properties may feature Nielsen proprietary measurement software, which will allow you to contribute to market research, such as Nielsen TV Ratings. To learn more about the information that Nielsen software may collect and your choices with regard to it, please see the Nielsen Digital Measurement Privacy Policy at http://www.nielsen.com/digitalprivacy.

How we use your information

We may use your Personal Information and the Usage Information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the context of our relationship with you. We will use the personally identifying information collected on this Site for the following purposes:

To respond to your requests and to provide you with the Service; To respond to your inquiries and contact you about changes to this Site; To send you notices (for example, in the form of e-mails, newsletters, daily digest, dot dot dot, mailings, and the like); For any other purposes disclosed at the time the information is collected or to which you consent; and As otherwise specifically described in this Privacy Policy.

We may also use your information to improve our Site, and may use cookies and other information to enable us to customize your user experience. We may disclose to third parties aggregate data regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, our Site, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

We, like many businesses, sometimes hire other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, hosting services, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. We require such third parties to maintain the confidentiality of such information and use such information only as necessary to provide us with designated services. If we or all or substantially all of our assets are acquired, we expect that the information that we have collected, including personally identifying information, would be transferred along with our other business assets.

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is or may be causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of this Site, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

How we protect your information

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect the Personal Information and the Usage Information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet.

Links

This Site contains content, services, advertising and other materials that link to web sites operated by third parties. We have no control over those other sites, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them.

Children

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13 through the Services. If you are under 13, please do not give us any Personal Information. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children to never provide Personal Information through the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date stated at the top of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, and will post any changes on the Site as soon as they go into effect. By accessing the Site or using the Service after we make any such changes to this Privacy Policy, you are deemed to have accepted such changes. Please refer back to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.

How to opt out

<http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/>  

How to contact us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at justin@motiv31.com, “PRIVACY POLICY” in the subject line, or mail us at the following address:

GroovyHistory

101 West Broadway, Suite 300

San Diego, CA 92109

Last updated: November 7th 2017
